

NAZISH KANWAL

Nationality: Pakistan Age: 32

Wechat: Nazish_kanwal Phone: +92 3348406372

Email: nazish_kanwal1986@yahoo.com

Address: House No. K-90, Mohallah Pankha Sazaan, Raiti Bazar, Peshawar 25000, Khyber

Pakhtunkhwa, Pakistan.

Profile:

I am a Pakistani national. I hold Master's degree in Agricultural Economics & Management from China Agricultural University. I have over six years of teaching experience in Pakistan and China. I have also 2 years of management experience in a private company in Pakistan. I am currently seeking a job in a company or organization. My interests include teaching, management, marketing and research etc.

Education:

2014-2016

• Master in Agricultural Economics & Management,

College of Economics & Management Studies, China Agricultural University, Beijing – China.

2007-2009

• Master in Economics,

Frontier Women University, Peshawar – Pakistan

2004-2006

• Bachelor in Economics,

Government Frontier College for Girls, Peshawar – Pakistan

Work History:

Feb 2017 - March 2019

• Assistant Manager

Happy Furnishers, Islamabad, China

Jul 2016 - Dec 2016

• Foreign English Teacher

ABC English School, Liangxiang, Beijing, China

April 2010 - August 2014

• Science Teacher

Sir Syed Public School, Peshawar, Pakistan

January 2008 - April 2009

• English Teacher

Uswah Model School, Peshawar, Pakistan

Training and Workshops:

- Attended workshop on Teaching Methodologies organized by Oxford University Press.
- Awarded certificate of Functional English Course.
- Attended two weeks training program on "First Aid".
- Served as a member in Literary Society, Frontier Women University, Peshawar, Pakistan.

Honors and Awards:

• Awarded full Chinese Government Scholarship for Master Degree Program in Agricultural Economics at China Agricultural University (2014-2016) by the China Scholarship Council.

Research Publications:

• 10 research publications in well-reputed international journals.

Languages:

English - Fluent
Urdu - Native
Chinese - Good

Computer:

- MS Office
- SPSS
- Stata
- Social Media apps and websites

References:

• Will be furnished upon request